export const QuizDataGetMock = {
    status: "Success",
    message: null,
    data: {
        topic: {
            id: 185,
            title: "Human Resource Management (HRM)",
            description: null,
            instructions: null,
            topic_url: "https://mcqmate.com/topic/human-resource-management",
        },
        sets: [23, 24, 25],
        attempts: {
            23: [
                {
                    date: "12 days ago",
                    right_mcqs: 16,
                    wrong_mcqs: 4,
                },
                {
                    date: "3 days ago",
                    right_mcqs: 10,
                    wrong_mcqs: 10,
                },
                {
                    date: "3 days ago",
                    right_mcqs: 13,
                    wrong_mcqs: 7,
                },
            ],
            25: [
                {
                    right_mcqs: 16,
                    wrong_mcqs: 4,
                },
                {
                    right_mcqs: 10,
                    wrong_mcqs: 10,
                },
                {
                    right_mcqs: 13,
                    wrong_mcqs: 7,
                },
            ],
        },
        mcqs: [
            {
                id: 77705,
                question:
                    "Rewards offered to labours involved in production, are categorized as:",
                a: "Salary",
                b: "Fringe benefits",
                c: "Wage",
                d: "Commission",
                e: null,
                answer: "c",
                instructions: null,
                discussion_url:
                    "https://mcqmate.com/discussion/77705/rewards-offered-to-labours-involved-in-production-are-categorized-as",
            },
            {
                id: 101392,
                question:
                    "………. is the process of allocating tasks among its members for achieving organizational\nobjectives",
                a: "Organizing",
                b: "directing",
                c: "staffing",
                d: "controlling",
                e: null,
                answer: "a",
                instructions: null,
                discussion_url:
                    "https://mcqmate.com/discussion/101392/%E2%80%A6%E2%80%A6%E2%80%A6-is-the-process-of-allocating-tasks-among-its-members-for-achieving-organizational-objectives",
            },
            {
                id: 77560,
                question:
                    "Which of the following method includes the exchange of information\nbetween organizational member & the applicant through a goal-oriented conversation?",
                a: "Counselling simulations",
                b: "Vocational interest test",
                c: "Role playing",
                d: "Employment interview",
                e: null,
                answer: "d",
                instructions: null,
                discussion_url:
                    "https://mcqmate.com/discussion/77560/which-of-the-following-method-includes-the-exchange-of-information-between-organizational-member-the-applicant-through-a-goal-oriented-conversation",
            },
            {
                id: 139979,
                question:
                    "Which of the following is the functions of personnel management",
                a: "Managerial function",
                b: "Operative function",
                c: "Both a & b",
                d: "All of these",
                e: null,
                answer: "c",
                instructions: null,
                discussion_url:
                    "https://mcqmate.com/discussion/139979/which-of-the-following-is-the-functions-of-personnel-management",
            },
            {
                id: 140042,
                question:
                    "Four step instructional related to which method of T & D",
                a: "JIT",
                b: "Coaching",
                c: "Monitoring",
                d: "All of these",
                e: null,
                answer: "a",
                instructions: null,
                discussion_url:
                    "https://mcqmate.com/discussion/140042/four-step-instructional-related-to-which-method-of-t-d",
            },
            {
                id: 139901,
                question: "3600 feedback involves appraisal by",
                a: "Line managers",
                b: "Subordinate",
                c: "Superiors",
                d: "Anyone who is directly in contact with appraisee",
                e: null,
                answer: "d",
                instructions: null,
                discussion_url:
                    "https://mcqmate.com/discussion/139901/3600-feedback-involves-appraisal-by",
            },
            {
                id: 101428,
                question: "Bonus comes under the category of",
                a: "Wages",
                b: "allowances",
                c: "incentives",
                d: "fringe benefits",
                e: null,
                answer: "c",
                instructions: null,
                discussion_url:
                    "https://mcqmate.com/discussion/101428/bonus-comes-under-the-category-of",
            },
            {
                id: 139975,
                question:
                    "_______________________adds additional motivation to a job to make it more rewarding",
                a: "Entertainment",
                b: "Social benefits",
                c: "Job enrichment",
                d: "None of these",
                e: null,
                answer: "c",
                instructions: null,
                discussion_url:
                    "https://mcqmate.com/discussion/139975/adds-additional-motivation-to-a-job-to-make-it-more-rewarding",
            },
            {
                id: 143134,
                question:
                    "Which of the following work behaviors is considered “generic” or important to all jobs?",
                a: "industriousness",
                b: "intelligence",
                c: "experience",
                d: "morality",
                e: null,
                answer: "a",
                instructions: null,
                discussion_url:
                    "https://mcqmate.com/discussion/143134/which-of-the-following-work-behaviors-is-considered-%E2%80%9Cgeneric%E2%80%9D-or-important-to-all-jobs",
            },
            {
                id: 139976,
                question:
                    "_________ is concerned with proper utilization with the management and proper utilization of human resources for attaining organizational goals ",
                a: "Employment",
                b: "Personal management",
                c: "Recruitment",
                d: "All of these",
                e: null,
                answer: "b",
                instructions: null,
                discussion_url:
                    "https://mcqmate.com/discussion/139976/is-concerned-with-proper-utilization-with-the-management-and-proper-utilization-of-human-resources-for-attaining-organizational-goals",
            },
            {
                id: 139900,
                question:
                    "The origin of personnel management was an outcome of",
                a: "Welfare workers",
                b: "Legislation relating factory Reform",
                c: "The govt. notification",
                d: "The work of 19th century social reformers and employee",
                e: null,
                answer: "a",
                instructions: null,
                discussion_url:
                    "https://mcqmate.com/discussion/139900/the-origin-of-personnel-management-was-an-outcome-of",
            },
            {
                id: 143013,
                question:
                    "In which of the following kinds of interview, the questions are predetermined?",
                a: "Panel",
                b: "Stress",
                c: "Group",
                d: "Structural",
                e: null,
                answer: "d",
                instructions: null,
                discussion_url:
                    "https://mcqmate.com/discussion/143013/in-which-of-the-following-kinds-of-interview-the-questions-are-predetermined",
            },
            {
                id: 143083,
                question:
                    "In the ………………… the trainee is given an opportunity to handle and observe the job by doing it themselves.",
                a: "On-the-job training",
                b: "Off-the-job training",
                c: "Training for improvement",
                d: "None of the above",
                e: null,
                answer: "a",
                instructions: null,
                discussion_url:
                    "https://mcqmate.com/discussion/143083/in-the-%E2%80%A6%E2%80%A6%E2%80%A6%E2%80%A6%E2%80%A6%E2%80%A6%E2%80%A6-the-trainee-is-given-an-opportunity-to-handle-and-observe-the-job-by-doing-it-themselves",
            },
            {
                id: 181581,
                question:
                    "The famous definition of ‘personality’ as “the dynamic organization within the individual of those psychological systems that determine his unique adjustments to his environment” – is given by",
                a: "Theodore T. Herbert",
                b: "Sigmund Freud",
                c: "Gordon Allport",
                d: "James Watson",
                e: null,
                answer: "c",
                instructions: null,
                discussion_url:
                    "https://mcqmate.com/discussion/181581/the-famous-definition-of-%E2%80%98personality%E2%80%99-as-%E2%80%9Cthe-dynamic-organization-within-the-individual-of-those-psychological-systems-that-determine-his-unique-adjustments-to-his-environment%E2%80%9D-%E2%80%93-is-given-by",
            },
            {
                id: 140067,
                question:
                    "Which of  the following are the internal source of recruitment",
                a: "Promotion",
                b: "Trainees",
                c: "Transfers",
                d: "All of these",
                e: null,
                answer: "d",
                instructions: null,
                discussion_url:
                    "https://mcqmate.com/discussion/140067/which-of-the-following-are-the-internal-source-of-recruitment",
            },
            {
                id: 139893,
                question: "Process of manpower planning consists",
                a: "Forecasting",
                b: "Development implementation",
                c: "Controlling",
                d: "All of these",
                e: null,
                answer: "d",
                instructions: null,
                discussion_url:
                    "https://mcqmate.com/discussion/139893/process-of-manpower-planning-consists",
            },
            {
                id: 143033,
                question:
                    "Criticisms of training are based on the understanding that ",
                a: "It is challenging method of learning",
                b: "It is linked with short term goals",
                c: "It is not liked by trade unions",
                d: "All of the above",
                e: null,
                answer: "a",
                instructions: null,
                discussion_url:
                    "https://mcqmate.com/discussion/143033/criticisms-of-training-are-based-on-the-understanding-that",
            },
            {
                id: 77555,
                question:
                    "Which of the given statement reflects the Relationship between HRM &\nManagement?",
                a: "Both are same",
                b: "Management is one aspect of HRM",
                c: "HRM is one aspect of Management",
                d: "No relationship exists",
                e: null,
                answer: "c",
                instructions: null,
                discussion_url:
                    "https://mcqmate.com/discussion/77555/which-of-the-given-statement-reflects-the-relationship-between-hrm-management",
            },
            {
                id: 181625,
                question: "Who laid the foundation of HRM practice?",
                a: "Elton Mayo",
                b: "Roethlisberger and Dickinson",
                c: "Peter Drucker and Douglas McGregor",
                d: "David C. McClelland.",
                e: null,
                answer: "c",
                instructions: null,
                discussion_url:
                    "https://mcqmate.com/discussion/181625/who-laid-the-foundation-of-hrm-practice",
            },
            {
                id: 181493,
                question:
                    "______ is any process that provides greater authority the sharing of relevant information and the provision of control over factors affecting job performance.",
                a: "Collective Bargaining",
                b: "Empowerment",
                c: "Participation",
                d: "None of the above",
                e: null,
                answer: "b",
                instructions: null,
                discussion_url:
                    "https://mcqmate.com/discussion/181493/is-any-process-that-provides-greater-authority-the-sharing-of-relevant-information-and-the-provision-of-control-over-factors-affecting-job-performance",
            },
        ],
    },
};
